skyverge.com 2016-12-07

# Privacy Policy - SkyVerge

### Website Visitors

Like most website operators, SkyVerge collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. SkyVerge’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how SkyVerge.com’s visitors use its website. From time to time, SkyVerge may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

SkyVerge also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. SkyVerge does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

### Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to SkyVerge’s website choose to interact with SkyVerge in ways that require SkyVerge to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that SkyVerge gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who register for an account to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with SkyVerge – by purchasing our plugins, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information  
required to process those transactions. In each case, SkyVerge collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with SkyVerge.

SkyVerge does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. Visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying  
information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

### Aggregated Statistics

SkyVerge may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, SkyVerge may monitor plugin downloads or number of comments. SkyVerge may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, SkyVerge does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

### Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

SkyVerge discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on SkyVerge’s behalf or to provide services available at SkyVerge’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others.

Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using SkyVerge’s website, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. SkyVerge will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone.

Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, SkyVerge discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only in response to a subpoena, court order or other governmental request, or when SkyVerge believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property  
or rights of SkyVerge, third parties or the public at large.

If you are a registered user of a SkyVerge website and have supplied your email address, SkyVerge may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with SkyVerge and our products. We primarily use our blog to communicate this type of information, so we expect  
to keep this type of email to a minimum.

If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we  
reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. SkyVerge takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

### Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time  
the visitor returns. SkyVerge uses cookies to help SkyVerge identify and track visitors, their usage of the SkyVerge website, and their website access preferences. SkyVerge visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using SkyVerge’s website, with the drawback that certain features of SkyVerge’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

### Business Transfers

If SkyVerge, or substantially all of its assets, were acquired, or in the unlikely event that SkyVerge goes out of business or enters bankruptcy, user information would be one of the assets that is transferred or acquired by a third party. You acknowledge that such transfers may occur, and that any acquirer of SkyVerge may continue to use your personal information as set forth in this policy.

### Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, SkyVerge may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and at SkyVerge’s sole discretion. SkyVerge encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

* * *

This Privacy Policy is used and adapted via a [Creative Commons Sharealike](http://creativecommons.org/licenses/by-sa/2.5/) license from _[Automattic](http://github.com/automattic/legalmattic)_. You can [view it here](http://github.com/automattic/legalmattic).
